ILGWU Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation Records 5780/114
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation Records
1974-1982
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU)
5780/114
16 cubic feet
16 linear ft.
Records (documents), photographs.
Contains application files from shops and workers therein to participate in the Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation's training program, financial records, and reports. Application files include applications from shops for certification with AFTRC, agreements between the AJTRC and shops for on-the-job-training, applications from individuals for enrollment in the AJTRC, and related correspondence. Financial records include invoices and related correspondence. Reports address conditions in the apparel industry.
5520629
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
C. Berne, July 06, 2009
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 15, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Biographical / Historical
Under contract granted by the United States Department of Labor in April 1979, the Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation was a non-profit organization, directed by a board composed of labor and management representatives, that provided training for 1500 sewing machine operators in the garment industry in the United States. The training program operated under the provisions of Title III of the Comprehensive Employment and Training Act.
Employers engaged in women's apparel manufacturing, with requisite staffing, records of work retention, and wages and benefits for workers, were eligible to apply to participate in the program. If accepted, the employer was then required to agree to pay at least $3.40 per hour, and the AJT &RC would pay $1.70 per hour per trainee. The Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation maintained a staff of Project Coordinators to "help the employers locate trainees, help fill out the necessary forms if requested, and verify the requests for reimbursement made by the employers."
Scope and Contents
Contains application files from shops and workers therein to participate in the Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation's training program, financial records, and reports.
Application files contain documentation from the beginning of a shops enrollment in the training program to the trainees' notice of the end of the program, though not every company file is complete. Applications for certification with the AJTRC include basic data about the company (whether a contractor or manufacturer), including information on the types of garments produced, number of operators, number of those operators receiving W2 forms and fringe benefits, existing training resources, and anticipated need for trainees.
Companies accepted into the program entered into an agreement with the AJTRC for on-the-job-training. These agreements detailed the number and type of positions (piecework or timework, entry-level or upgrading), the kind of training (sewing machine operation, pressing, etc.), dates and duration of the training program, the amount of payment to the firm from the AJTRC, and other relevant information.
Also included in applications on behalf of individuals who sought to enroll in the training program, and related correspondence. These individual applications provide detailed profiles about workers, including name, age, address, information on education, family, veteran, income, and labor force status, race and ethnicity, disability, and criminal offences, as well as whether the applicant was a displaced homemaker, was a migrant or seasonal farm worker, or received public assistance.
Monthly invoices, sent from the firm to the AJTRC, contain the names of program participants (enrollees and trainers), hours worked, and earnings. In some instances, "Project Coordinator checklists" accompany invoices and indicate whether the firms were adhering to the conditions of their agreement with the AJTRC. Reports address conditions in the apparel industry, and document the work of the Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation's Project Coordinators.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records
Women's clothing industry--United States.; Women's clothing industry--New York (State)--New York.; Clothing workers--Labor unions--United States.; Clothing workers--Labor unions--New York (State)--New York.; Clothing workers--United States.; Clothing workers--New York (State)--New York.; Industrial relations--United States.; Industrial relations--New York (State)--New York.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.; Apparel, Job Training and Research Corporation
5520629
- Mohawk Manufacturing Inc. 1-131508-CM041, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Mohawk Manufacturing Enrollee/Applications 1-131508-CM041, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Mohawk Manufacturing Company Inc. 1-131508-CM043, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Mohawk Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-131508-CM043, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Mohawk Manufacturing 1-131508-CM044, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Mohawk Manufacturing Forms 1-131508-CM044, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Mohawk West Contract 131508-0R041, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Mohawk West Enrollee Applications 1-131508-0R041, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Little Frocks 1-120920-LF011, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Little Frocks Enrollee Applications 1-120920-LF011, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Lily Manufacturing 1-120912-LL031, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Lily Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-120912-LL031, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- North Berwick Mills Enrollee Applications, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Barad and Co. Hours and Pay Record (Box 1, Folder 14)
- D+J Dress 1-041004-NY011, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- D+J Dress Enrollee Applications 1-041004-NY011, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- D+J Dress 1-041004-NY012, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- D+J Dress Enrollee Applications 1-041004-NY012, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- DOL-ETA, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Gemini Corp 3-070513-SF041, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Gemini Corp Enrollee Applications 3-070513-SF041, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Glasgow Manufacturing 2-0701201-GG231, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Glasgow Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 2-0701201-GG231, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- D. Glasgow 2-040712-NY011, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- D. Glasgow Enrollee Applications 2-040712-NY011, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Gramercy Mills, Inc 2-071801-PA021, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Gramercy Mills, Inc. Enrollee Applications 2-071801-PA021, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Greendell Manufacturing Corp 1-071805-NY011, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Greendell Manufacturing Corp. Enrollee Applications 1-071805-NY011, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Green Mountain 1-071805-NE191, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Green Mountain Enrollee Applications 1-071805-NE191, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Green Mountain 1-071805-NE192, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Green Mountain Enrollee Applications 1-071805-NE192, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Green Mountain Sportswear 1-071805-NE193, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Green Mountain Enrollee Applications 1-071805-NE193, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Green Mountain Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-071805-NE194, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Green Mountain Sportswear 1-071805-NE195, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Green Mountain Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-071805-NE195, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Green Mountain Sportswear 1-071805-NE196, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Green Mountain Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-071805-NE196, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Hamilton Dress, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Hamilton Dress Enrollee Applications 1-080113-NY011, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Hilton Coat and Suit 1-080912-BU021, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Hilton Coat and Suit Enrollee Applications 1-080912-BU021, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Hodes Dress 1-081504-PF021, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Hodes Dress Enrollee Applications 1-081504-PF021, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Hodes Dress 1-081504-PF022, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Hodes Dress Enrollee Applications 1-081504-PF022, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Hudson Mills 2-082104-HU191, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Hudson Mills Enrollee Applications 2-082104-HU191, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Hudson Mills 2-082104-HU192, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Indiana Sportswear 1-091404-CL093, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Indiana Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-091404-CL093, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Indiana Sportswear 1-091404-CL094, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Indiana Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-091404-CL094, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Indiana Sportswear 1-091404-CB091, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Indiana Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-091404-CB091, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Indiana Sportswear 1-091404-CB092, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Indiana Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-091404-CB092, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- JB Sportswear 1-100219-FR041, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- JB Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-100219-FR041, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- J+R Dress 1-101804-WY031, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- J+R Dress Enrollee Applications 1-101804-WY031, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- J+R Dress 1-101804-WY032, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- J+R Dress Enrollee Applications 1-101804-WY032, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- J+T Sportswear 1-102019-QU041, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- J+T Sportswear 1-102019-QU042, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- J+T Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-102019-QU041, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- J+T Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-102019-QU042, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- J+T Sportswear 1-102019-QU043, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Jane Martin 1-100105-MV011, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Jane Martin 1-100105-MV011, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Jane Martin Enrollee Applications 1-100105-MV011, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- JoAnn Apparel 1-101501-EB031, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- JoAnn Apparel Enrollee Applications 1-101501-EB032, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- JoAnn Apparel 1-101501-EB032, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- JoAnn Apparel Enrollee Applications 1-101501-EB031, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Joyce Sportswear 2-100114-GR091, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Joyce Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-100114-GR091, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Jay Rose Dress 1-100125-MV011, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Jay Rose Enrollee Applications 1-100125-MV011, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Joel Manufacturing 1-100512-WB031, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Joel Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-100512-WB031, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Joey Rome Fashions 1-101505-MV011, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Joey Rome Enrollee Applications 1-101505-MV011, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Joey Rome Fashions 1-101505-MV012, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Joey Rome Enrollee Applications 1-101505-MV012, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Jomar Manufacturing 1-101513-AL031, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Jomar Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-101513-AL031, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Jomar of Glens Falls 1-101513-GF011, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Jomar of Glens Falls Enrollee Applications 1-101513-GF011, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Junior House 2-102114-MW111, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Junior House 2-102114-MW112, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Junior House Enrollee Applications 2-102114-MW111, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Junior House Enrollee Applications 2-102114-MW112, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- KDK Trimming and Novelty 2-190613-PS021, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- KDK Trimming and Novelty 2-190613-PS021, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Kaychester 1-110125-PC011, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Kaychester Enrollee Applications 1-110125-PC011, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- LA Dress 1-120104-WB031, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- LA Dress Enrollee Applications 1-120104-WB031, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Lackawanna Dress 1-12003-LA031, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Lackawanna Dress Enrollee Applications 1-120103-LA031, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Liberty Frocks 1-120902-NY011, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Liberty Frocks Enrollee Applications 1-120902-NY011, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Lisa Marie Sportswear 1-120919-PH021, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Lisa Marie Enrollee Applications 1-120919-PH021, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Lisa Sportswear 1-120919-WB031, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Lisa Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-120919-WB031, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Lisa Sportswear 1-120919-WB032, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Lisa Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-120919-WB032, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Long Island Pattern Services 1-121414-NN011 Renewal, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Long Island Pattern Services Enrollee Applications 1-121514-NN011 Renewal, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Lowell Lingerie 1-121423-LO041, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Lowell Lingerie 1-121523-LO042, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Lowell Lingerie Enrollee Applications 1-121523-LO041, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Lucky Star 2-122103-NY011, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Lucky Star Enrollee Applications 2-122103-NY011, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Lucky Star 2-122103-NY012, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Lucky Star Enrollee Applications 2-122103-NY012, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Maidenform 2-130109-BA021, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Maidenform Enrollee Applications 2-130109-BA021, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Majestic Shapes 2-130110-NY011, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Majestic Shapes Enrollee Applications 2-130110-NY011, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Majestic Shapes 2-130110-NY012, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Majestic Shapes Enrollee Applications 2-130110-NY012, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Malden Mills 2-130112-LA041, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Malden Mills Enrollee Applications 2-130112-LA041, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Malden Mills 2-130112-LA042, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Malden Mills Enrollee Applications 2-13011-LA041, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Malden Mills 2-130112-LA043, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Malden Mills Enrollee Applications 2-130112-LA043, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Malden Mills 2-120112-LA044, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Malden Mills Enrollee Applications 2-130112-LA044, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Malden Mills 2-130112-LA045, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Malden Mills Enrollee Applications 2-130112-LA045, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Malden Mills 2-130112-LA046, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Malden Mills Enrollee Applications 2-130112-LA046, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Malden Mills 2-130112-LA047, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Malden Mills Enrollee Applications 2-130112-LA047, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Manly Manufacturing 1-130114-NB041 Renewal, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Manly Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-130114-NB041 Renewal, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Mar-Jo 1-130118-EO021, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Mar-Jo Enrollee Applications 1-130118-EO021, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Mar-Lil 1-130118-NB041, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Mar-Lil Enrollee Applications 1-130118-NB041, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Mi-Li 1-130912-QU041, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Mi-Li Enrollee Applications 1-130912-QU041, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Melissa Lingerie 1-130912-PS021, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Melissa Lingerie Enrollee Applications 1-130912-PS021, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Nancy Dee Dress 1-140114-EX031, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Nancy Dee Dress Enrollee Applications 1-140114-EX031, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Nanette Undies 2-140114-NY011, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Nanette Undies Enrollee Applications 2-140114-NY011, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- New Bedford Manufacturing 1-140523-NB041, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- New Bedford Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-140523-NB041, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- North Berwick Mills 2-020518-NB241 Renewal, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- North Berwick Mills Enrollee Applications 2-020518-NB241 Renewal, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- North Berwick Mills 2-020518-NB242, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- North Berwick Mills Enrollee Applications 2-020518-NB242, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- E & B Dress 1-050204-CB031, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- E & B Dress Enrollee Applications 1-050204-CB031, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Family Garment 1-060113-SC031 Renewal, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Family Garment Enrollee Applications 1-060113-SC031 Renewal, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Family Garment 1-060113-SC032, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Family Garment Enrollee Applications 1-060113-SC032, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Family Sportswear 1-060113-FR041, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Family Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-060113-FR042, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Family Sportswear 1-060113-FR042, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Family Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-060113-FR041, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Fashion Affiliates 2-060119-FR194, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Fashion Affiliates Enrollee Applications 2-060119-FR194, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Fashion Affiliates 2-060119-FR195, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Fashion Affiliates Enrollee Applications 2-060119-FR195, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Franklin Apparel 2-060119-FR196, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Franklin Apparel Enrollee Applications 2-060119-FR196, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Fashion Affiliates 2-060119-FR191, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Fashion Affiliates Enrollee Applications 2-060119-FR192, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Fashion Affiliates 2-060119-FR192, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Fashion Affiliates Enrollee Applications 2-060119-FR191, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Fashion Affiliates 2-060119-FR193, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Fashion Affiliates Enrollee Applications 2-060119-FR193, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Fashion Affiliates (OV Dress) 2-060119-NB041, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Fashion Affiliates (OV Dress) Enrollee Applications 2-060119-NB041, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Felco 2-060512-NY011, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Felco Enrollee Applications 2-060512-NY011, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Fisher Sportswear 1-060919-BR041, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Fisher Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-060919-BR041, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Fisher Sportswear 1-060919-BR042, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Fisher Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-060919-BR042, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Fisher Sportswear 1-060919-BR043, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Fisher Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-060919-BR043, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Foreman Manufacturing 1-061518-WM021, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Foreman Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-061518-WM021, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- David Stevens 1-040122-BL021, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- David Stevens Enrollee Applications 1-040122-BL021, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- David Stevens 1-040122-BL22, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- David Stevens Enrollee Applications 1-040122-BL022, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- DeSantis Dress 2-040519-VI021, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- DeSantis Dress Enrollee Applications 2-040519-VI021, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- DeSantis Dress 2-040519-VI022, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- DeSantis Dress Enrollee Applications 2-040519-VI022, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Domenico 1-041513-LY041, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Domenico Enrollee Applications 1-041513-LY041, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Domenico 1-041513-LY042, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Domenico Enrollee Applications 1-041513-LY042, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Domenico 1-041513-LY043, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Domenico Enrollee Applications 1-041513-LY043, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Domenico 1-041513-LY044, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Domenico Enrollee Applications 1-041513-LY044, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Domenico 1-041513-LY045, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Domenico Enrollee Applications 1-041513-LY045, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Doris Ann Fashions 1-041518-UC021, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Doris Ann Fashions Enrollee Applications 1-041518-UC021, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Duo Sportswear 1-042115-BO041, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Duo Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-042115-BO041, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Cheryl Dress 1-030805-FR041, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Cheryl Dress 1-030805-FR042, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Cheryl Dress Enrollee Applications 1-030805-FR041, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Cheryl Dress Enrollee Applications 1-030805-FR042, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Cincy Sportswear 1-030914-CN251, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Cincy Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-030914-CN251, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Colebrook Terry Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-031512-LE036, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Colebrook Terry Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-031512-LE031, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Colebrook Terry Manufacturing 1-031512-LE032, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Colebrook Terry Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-030512-LE032, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Colebrook Terry Manufacturing 1-031512-LE033, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Colebrook Terry Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-031512-LE033, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Colebrook Terry Manufacturing 1-031512-LE034, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Colebrook Terry Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-031512-LE034, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Colebrook Terry Manufacturing 1-031512-LE035, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Colebrook Terry Manufacturing 1-031512-LE031, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Colebrook Terry Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-031512-LE035, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Colebrook Terry Manufacturing 1-031512-LE036, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Colebrook Terry Manufacturing 1-031512-LE037, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Colebrook Terry Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-031512-LE037, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Clifford Manufacturing 1-031209-CL031, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Clifford Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-031209-CL031, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Concord Manufacturing 1-031514-MO071, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Concord Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-031514-MO071, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Cottage Tailor 2-031520-WS041, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Cottage Tailor Enrollee Applications 2-031520-WS041, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Cottage Tailor Enrollee Applications 2-031520-WS042, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Cottage Tailor 2-031520-WS042, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Cottage Tailor 2-031520-WS043, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Cottage Tailor Enrollee Applications 2-031520-WS043, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Country Miss 2-031521-BR141, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Country Miss 2-031521-ET031, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 32)